kirkal.com 2013-04-10

# Kirkal-Connect you with ur Friends & Relatives

Kirkal.com is a social networking site. The kirkal’s privacy policy governs the collection, use and disclosure of personal information you submit to kirkal.com.

Personal information is one that uniquely identifiable to you, like your name, email address, address, date of birth, and other information that is of personal in nature.

 **Information collection**

When you visit Kirkal we collect two types of information: personal information you knowingly choose to disclose that is collected by us and Website usage information collected by us as you interact with our Website. 

When you register with Kirkal, you provide us with certain personal information, such as your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your date of birth, your gender, and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.  
When you enter Kirkal, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all Kirkal visitors. In addition to this, we store certain information from your browser using "cookies." A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. We use session ID cookies to confirm that users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the user closes the browser. By default, the cookie stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to Kirkal. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature.

 **Use of Information**

Your profile information, your name, photo will be displayed to people in the networks based on your selection of privacy setting. We may use your name and email address to send notification, if someone contacted you in kirkal.

If you choose to use our invitation service to invite your friend to kirkal, we may ask you to provide information such as friend’s email address to send the invitation. Kirkal will not use this email address for any other communication besides invitation and invitation reminders.

Kirkal.com give restricted access to site information by third party search engine “crawlers” like Google, Yahoo, MSN etc., kirkal.com take necessary action to block access by the search engine crawlers to personal information beyond your name, profile pictures and your profile page data (based on your privacy settings) 

In kirkal.com, certain information you post or share with third parties (like friends or any member in your network), such as personal information, messages, comments, photos, videos, discussions in forums, groups or any other information may be shared with other user in accordance with your privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting messages, comments, photos, videos, Forums, groups or on any other place, this information may become publicly available.  

 **Children Under Age 16**

Kirkal.com does not knowingly collect any personal information from anyone under the age of 16 or knowingly allow such persons to register. Kirkal.com is not intended for anyone under the age of 16. If you are under age 16, please do not attempt to use kirkal.com. 

If you are parent of child under the age of 16 and believe that we have information from or about your child, please contact us at: privacy@kirkal.com 

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

Kirkal does not rent, share, or sell personal information about you with third party or nonaffiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We will disclose information in response to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. We may disclose information, if we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected illegal activities or fraud, situations involving the physical safety of any person, violations of kirkal's terms of use, or as otherwise required by applicable law.

 **Conflict resolution**

We are committed to resolving disputes as soon as possible and shall endeavor to resolve all disputes brought to our notice in keeping with the mechanism prescribed.

 **Changes in our privacy policy**

From time to time we may make changes to our privacy policy. If we make changes, we will post them on our site to make users aware of what the changes are, so users will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and when we may disclose it. A user is bound by any changes to the policy when she or he uses the site after those changes have been posted

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, please contact us at: privacy@kirkal.com
